Juan Lemos

Personal Information

Name: Juan Lemos Web: <u>juanlemos.com</u>

linkedin.com/in/juan-lemos



Summary

Software engineer graduated from Universidad Católica del Uruguay. Passionate about learning, making questions and solving problems.

Interested in decision making and business management.

I have worked for more than 2 years into the software development industry with American clients, in diverse teams. My tasks has been to

align the software solutions

with the client's needs and thinking in the medium- and long-term

consequences.

Skills

Programming:

- React
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- NodeJS
- SQL
- Android
- Java
- Swift

Others:

- English
- Portuguese
- Decision making
- Communication
- Problem-Solving

Experience

Full stack developer at Código Del Sur Aug 2017 – Present

Scholarship at ICT4V (Information and Communication Technologies for Verticals) Sep 2016 – Jul 2017

Education

IEEM Business school – PJP business programs 2019

Universidad Católica Del Uruguay – Computer engineer 2013 - 2017